[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
[Claire] Emilia, what's going on?!
[Emilia] I'm tracking any possible
evidence against me.
Ivy Aguas is back, Auntie!
[Ivy] I'm here because I want
to keep an eye on you.
Sleep well, Arnaldo.
-[Emilia] Hi, Camia!
-What are you doing here?
You went through my files at the capitol?!
For what? To investigate me?
I won't let someone like you
put me behind bars!
Do you understand?!
[Emilia] Camia Cruz didn't
file the case against me?!
Who filed it?! Diego?!
I can just imagine if this goes south.
How will this affect your candidacy?
[Joselito] Emilia will be tried
because the evidence is strong
against her.
You will lose a daughter.
She gives you nothing.
In essence, you lose nothing.
Why will you kill for nothing?
[Ivy] Thank you, Judge Nazareno.
I believe in your cause
and your desire to expose
corrupt public officials.
[Emilia] Divine Oytengco
was seen with Diego Torillo!
Wait for them outside the restaurant
-and blow their car into pieces!
-[gunshot]
Make sure everyone is dead!
[Julio] From the very start,
there's only been one pest in this family!
Diego Torillo!
[Diego] Give us Emilia Ardiente-Torillo.
[police] We have a warrant of arrest.
[Ivy] As much as I'd like
to pity you, Emilia,
I won't because you deserve
to be in prison.
And I can't even celebrate
because seeking justice is not a game,
it's a responsibility.
[tense music continues]
Ardiente, you have a visitor.
Wow.
Look what the cat dragged in.
You look at home in here.
Really, Ivy? Come on.
You're actually making
fun of someone in jail?
Is that how low you can be?
Come on, give me a break.
What do you expect, Emilia?
You think I'd stop
just because you're in prison?
No way! It can't be.
This is the real nature
of our relationship.
We are forever like this.
[Emilia] How dare you!
-How dare you!
-[Ivy] Hey! Calm down!
Have you forgotten?
Remember, you once told me
while you were drunk at your rest house
that when you were still
the mayor, governor,
and queen of Poblacion Ardiente,
you were stealing millions
of government funds.
Now, you are dubbed
as "Emilia, the Corrupt Queen."
[Emilia] Politics is something
beyond what you can imagine.
It has its own perks.
And you can actually steal
billions of money.
-[Emilia laughing]
-Billions?
That's supposed to be a secret, okay?
You filthy witch!
You ratted me out! Shame on you!
You filthy animal! It's you!
You colluded with Diego Torillo!
I knew it!
[Claire] Julio, please talk to me!
They've imprisoned your daughter!
You should see her situation now!
[thuds loudly]
What do you want me to do?
Get her a high-caliber lawyer!
Emilia's case must be dismissed!
You're asking me to go against the law?
I have an election to win!
What will the people say
if I release my criminal daughter?!
[laughs]
-So now, you follow the law?
-Yes.
I may not be an Ardiente,
but I know all the monstrosities
of this family!
And none of those deeds
are punished by law!
You know that you can release Emilia.
Why, Julio?!
Why aren't you doing anything?
Why are you punishing your own daughter?!
Just shut up!
Who do you think you are, Claire?! Huh?
You're nothing
but Emilia's glorified help!
And now that she's gone,
you have no place in this household!
You better learn your place!
Yes! I know, I don't belong here!
I know your family is a bunch
of heartless criminals!
And I'm only here for Emilia!
If it weren't for her,
I already left this hellhole!
Remember this!
Remember this well, Julio!
The day will come
when you'll meet your demise!
Now that Arnaldo is in a coma
and Emilia in jail,
you're all alone.
You're going to die alone!
[tense music playing]
No one will remember you!
Even the town that is named after you
will forget you!
Dying is the furthest thing from my mind!
I've got too many things to do.
[sighs]
You freaking witch! I am so done with you!
Filthy witch! What's this for, huh?!
A box of charity?! I don't need that!
I don't need any of these!
I don't need your clothes!
I don't need your stuff!
[Emilia panting softly]
[laughing]
Well, Emilia, there's nothing I can do
if you suspect me
of putting you behind bars.
Actually, maybe you are destined
to be in jail!
Does it hurt, Emilia?
Well, it's exactly what you deserve.
You witch!
You'll pay for this! You'll pay for this!
You filthy witch, Ivy!
Yes, I am.
Well, anyway, will you be all right?
You better relax, okay?
Bye, Corruption Queen!
[screaming and grunting]
[chuckling]
-[laughing]
-[grunting]
[Emilia screaming]
-No, those are for you!
-[Emilia screaming]
Get her out!
[chuckling]
Bye, Corruption Queen!
Snake!
[tense music playing]
[whimpering]
-Why am I here?
-[whimpering]
[medical equipment beeping]
Could you leave us for a moment?
I will just call you if I need you.
Noted, sir.
[pensive music playing]
[Claire] You will be left alone!
You're going to die alone!
No one will remember you!
Even the town that is named after you
will forget you!
Wake up, Arnaldo.
You have to wake up.
You are an Ardiente.
And I do not allow you
nor give you the right to die.
You can't die.
What is happening to us?
My grandson in a coma,
my daughter in jail…
What's left in me
is being taken away by my enemies.
This cannot be.
I will defend our name!
I will protect
the family of Ardientes!
I'll come up with a plan
before all is lost.
The Ardiente family and Ardiente name…
shall never fall!
I will not allow it.
[slow tense music playing]
[voice prompt] The subscriber
cannot be reached.
Please try again--
The subscriber cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
Hey, you!
You! I need your phone!
I need to call somebody.
I'm sorry, ma'am, but the time
for phone calls is over.
What?!
Just lend me your phone.
It'll only take a minute.
I'm really sorry.
[grunting]
You good-for-nothing boy scout!
Open the cell and get out of my way!
-Papa!
-Yes.
Yes, my beautiful daughter. I'm here.
I'm so glad you came.
So, are you gonna
take me out of this limbo?
No.
What?!
I can't let you out. I mean, look at you.
You're all miserable and desperate.
Give me one good reason
why I should let you out.
Because I am your daughter!
That is not a good enough reason.
You know what, Emilia?
I was thinking,
you should take time to relax.
You know… Uh…
Take this opportunity
to assess your past actions.
And you can do it all
in the comfort of this jail.
As I was looking around coming in here,
taking it all in,
it's not a really that bad a place.
And one more thing.
Why would I help you
if you do nothing for me?
You're useless to me right now.
You might even do something worse
that will complicate my candidacy.
[sobs] You cannot abandon me, Papa!
You cannot!
Believe me, Emilia,
this is for our family's best interest.
But, Papa, I need to get out from here!
I need to win this case.
Please, Papa! Help me!
I'm sorry. Goodbye, my dear.
Papa! Please!
Papa!
Why are you doing this to me?!
All my life, you're doing this to me!
Why is it so difficult
for you to save me?!
for you to love me, Papa?!
What did I do
for you to treat me like this?!
You should have just killed me, Papa!
You should never have let me live
if you were just going to abandon me!
You've never done anything
but insult me and hurt me!
You should have just killed me!
You're a useless father!
[tense music playing]
Papa! [whimpering]
Please! Papa!
Papa!
Hey!
Remember this.
My daughter is in there.
Give her everything she wants.
I don't ever want to hear
that my daughter has been hurt.
Don't let anyone lay a finger on her.
[tense music playing]
[Ivy] Out of 18 villages,
ten are solid Ardiente supporters.
That's quite a lead.
You know, Ivy,
I will surely win if you help me.
Fifty million pesos.
That's all I need right now
to tip the scale to my favor.
The campaign period is over, Congressman?
Why do you need money?
Well, unless you're talking
about vote buying,
If that's what it takes
to paint the town red,
so be it.
If I help you, what will I get in return?
Arnaldo is in a coma. Emilia is in jail.
That leaves you and me.
I will become king
and you will be queen
of Poblacion Ardiente.
[chuckles]
Julio Ardiente is willing
to share the throne?
Now that I'm all alone in this fight,
I need to be sure of everyone's loyalty.
Ivy, I will weed out
all the bad grass and flowers,
those who wish to go against my reign.
Now, give it to me straight.
Are you going to accept my offer?
It's either you're with me
or you're against me.
[music intensifies]
[foreboding music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Ivy] Obviously, this question is a trap.
Do you think an old man like you
can fool me?
Congressman, my loyalty belongs to you.
It's all yours.
You are my governor
and you will surely win the election.
My, my, what an intricate web you spin.
Come into my parlor,
said the spider to the fly.
That Julio is despicable!
Ivy, don't let the Ardientes
use your money.
[Ivy] Of course, not.
I only said that
to convince him of my loyalty.
But I will never agree to fund
his election scheme.
Well then, tell me the time and location,
I'll go there and take your money back.
[tense music playing]
-[woman] Good morning, Miss Ivy.
-Good morning.
-[woman] Good morning, ma'am.
Good morning.
Gather everyone in the boardroom.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Now.
[Mr. Feliciano] Let me start, Miss Aguas.
Fifty million pesos is a lot of money
for additional marketing budget.
Mr. Feliciano, as 70-percent
owner of Aguas Realties,
I have the right to allocate
the budget to a worthy cause.
And besides, this won't even offset
the amount of money
that my investors brought in, remember?
[Mr. Castro] That's right, Mr. Feliciano.
Poblacion Ardiente
is a passion project of Miss Aguas.
It has potential for greater revenue.
But this is too much to risk!
Can't you see it?
[board members chattering]
Okay.
Maybe we should just vote on it?
All those in favor of my proposal,
you can raise your hands.
Well, I guess,
this matter is already settled,
Mr. Feliciano.
And one more thing,
I've decided to take an indefinite leave
because of pressing issues, Mr. Castro,
so I appoint you as OIC of Aguas Realties.
The board has already decided on this,
so I want you to report
everything company details.
And I expect the same loyalty
that you gave to Miss Prianka.
Of course, Miss Aguas.
But if you don't mind me asking,
how long will your project
in Poblacion Ardiente last?
Because frankly, it's taking so much time.
A few months more
and everything will be complete
as exactly planned.
-Emilia.
-[Emilia] Papa is so heartless!
He's a monster!
He left me here to die!
He said he won't help me!
And without Papa's help,
I will rot in here!
And I don't want that to happen!
[Raul] Don't worry. I'll help you.
[Emilia] Please, Jaguar.
Please help me.
I'll help you but on one condition.
From now on, you'll be mine
and you'll turn your back on your father.
We'll work together
to bring Julio Ardiente down.
I'll do anything just get me out of here!
I'll even turn my back
on my worthless father!
Get ready. We have a job to do.
Are we going to track down Madrigal?
No.
It's a new mission for us.
But some of you must stay here.
We need to be careful
'cause we're still on the radar.
Understood, boss.
[Ivy] Fifty million, as promised.
Impressive.
-Would you like to count it?
-Nah.
I trust you.
[thuds loudly]
Not so fast, Congressman.
I want to know where my money is going.
Do you really wanna know?
It's a task for my goons.
Don't worry, Col. Sanggano is my watchdog.
Besides, I can also endorse
your campaign, right?
Surely, they can't say no
to a beautiful woman.
[tense music playing]
[Damian] It was a fist fight,
but he shot me!
That filthy animal!
Raul, you're going to pay for this!
Boss, what about our pay?
Who were the idiots
that lost to Raul's men?!
-It's all of you, right?!
-Just kidding, boss.
A joke?
Do I look like I'm kidding?!
Do you think this is a comedy bar?!
Hey, you stand up!
Who told you to sit down?!
But you have a point, Panganiban.
We need to get back on Raul
for what he stole from me!
We'll drain his wealth!
What are you waiting for?!
-Move out! Now!
-[Panganiban] Yes, boss.
[groaning loudly]
Panganiban! Get me some painkillers!
[police] This man was caught for robbery.
[ominous music playing]
[thumps]
-Did you see those guys?
-[police] No, who are they?
-They look new here.
-Let's check on them.
[suspenseful music playing]
Who are you two?
-[thumps]
-[grunts loudly]
[henchman] Where's the key?
-Open the cell!
-[Emilia] What's going on?!
What's going on?!
-[thumps]
-[Emilia screams]
[henchman] Ma'am Emilia,
Jaguar ordered us to get you.
Let's go.
-Ma'am Emilia!
-[Emilia screams]
[gunshots]
[woman screaming]
-[gunshots]
-[Emilia screams]
Come on.
Oh my God!
[henchman 1] It's Boss Jaguar.
-[henchman 2] Boss Jaguar.
-Boss.
Jaguar.
[action music playing]
[gunshots]
[tires screeching]
[Ivy] Yes, Congressman.
I'm with Sanggano
and we're on our way to the village chiefs
to deliver the money.
[Ivy] Yes, Congressman.
Thank you.
As early as now,
I'd like to thank everyone
for your help in preventing
Julio's election scheme.
How sure are you
that there will be a vote-buying
between Julio and the village chiefs?
I have a credible source,
and I'm sure of it.
The people of Balete and San Narciso
became the bulwarks of Ardiente
because they already sold off their votes.
[Diego] That's why we need to catch them.
[tense music playing]
We are being followed.
-Who?
-Diego Torillo.
Let's do this.
-[Ivy] My God!
-[tires screeching]
[Fernan] Get down!
[Ivy] Oh my God! Sanggano!
[Ivy] What's going on?!
[man] Get down!
What's the matter?
Someone told us that you have money
to bribe village captains
for the election!
Stay out of this!
You're not a cop, so you can't arrest us!
-Put that down!
-We've got you surrounded!
You put that down now!
Come on, Sanggano! Do something!
[tense music playing]
Excuse me, Diego Torillo!
Don't you dare lay a hand on this money!
Sanggano!
Hands off me! Get off!
-[grunts]
-[man] Diego!
[both grunting]
[gunshot]
[thumps]
Sanggano!
Go away, Diego!
Don't you dare touch my money!
Hands off! It's mine!
[Diego] Come on, let's go! Let's go!
That's my money!
-[Diego] Let's go!
-[man] Hurry!
[Ivy] Hey! You thieves!
That's my money! Thieves!
Get up! You're all worthless!
[Ivy] There's no way in hell
that you'll exploit my money,
old man Julio.
[woman] Anna, I need to see Miss Camia!
[Anna] She's here.
-Auntie.
-[woman] Miss Camia!
Ivy and Diego were involved
in an encounter!
-[Anna] Huh?
-What?!
My goodness, what happened this time?!
-Anna, we need to contact Jepoy!
-Go ahead, Auntie.
[slow tense music playing]
Hey! Madrigal! No, no, no!
I asked you!
Where the hell are you going?!
You can't leave!
You still owe me for saving you!
Ma'am, I have to go. Please.
[scoffs] Where are you going?
Who will you save this time?
Is it Diego?
Or Camia Cruz?
Or Lily Cruz?
Who the hell is that girl?!
Is she the savior of this town?!
Ma'am, I know and I will never forget
that I owe you my life.
I always pay my debts!
But just this once, ma'am,
please let me go.
Please.
Okay.
[Ivy] Hey, Col. Sanggano! Wake up!
You're pretty useless for a colonel!
[Sanggano] Where's Diego?!
-Where is he?!
-Where do you think?!
He's gone now!
Gone with my money!
We need to go after that bastard!
We'll both get in trouble
with the Congressman!
You go after him yourself!
I can't believe you lost to Diego!
Go after him and retrieve my money!
Stop staring! Leave!
Now!
-[Sanggano] Let's go!
-[Ivy] Get back my 50 million!
You're useless, Colonel!
Hurry!
[chuckles]
[phone dialing]
Diego.
Take care of the money.
We already secured it.
Julio can never use this for his schemes.
Thanks, Diego. Be careful.
[phone ringing]
-Mom?
-Lily.
Lily, my dear.
Are you safe?!
I heard you and Diego had an encounter
with Ardientes' men. Where are you?!
Mom, don't worry. I'm safe.
I'm just opposite the municipal hall
in Sitio Rabino.
You don't need to pick me up.
Promise me you won't--
[call hangs up]
What's wrong, Miss Camia?
Lily said she's across
from the Sitio Rabino hall.
Do you know where it is?
Yes, I do. I'll take us there.
Diego, it would be better
if we surrender the money to the police.
Leave it to me, Fernan.
What's important is that Julio
can never use this money
in his election scheme.
[tense music playing]
[Damian] You three go there.
You two, that way.
-Yes, boss.
-Move it.
[henchman] Hey, fake Jaguar!
What are you doing here?!
[Damian] Where is the fake Jaguar?
Kill him!
You are.
-Oh, it's me.
-[laughing]
Surrender your gun.
Oh! Don't shoot!
You'll wake everyone up.
-Just surrender your gun?
-[grunts]
[thuds]
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
[Damian panting]
[Emilia] Thank God, Jaguar.
I can't believe this! I am finally free!
Free and away from them!
I cannot believe this!
Jaguar, thank you. Thank you so much.
[Raul] Emilia,
no one will hurt you anymore.
I won't let your bastard father
make you cry again.
As long as the Jaguar is around,
no one can hurt you.
Thank you, Jaguar.
You know, I've never felt
so loved in my life.
You're the only one
who made me feel this way.
Thank you very much.
-[line rings]
-Hello?
Yes, this is Clarita de Guzman
of the Ardientes.
Madam, there's something you need to know.
[Julio] And who are you calling?
[tense music playing]
It's none of your business.
[thuds and clatters]
What's wrong with you, Julio?!
You little sneaky rat!
You take me for a fool, huh?!
Do you think I'm stupid?!
I know why you've been enduring
in this family
and why you're staying
despite all the madness!
It's because you're an informant!
Who are you working for?
-Ivy Aguas?!
-[laughing]
You're so vain, Julio!
Did it ever occur to you
that Emilia became corrupt because of you?
Because of this family?!
And don't tell me
that you didn't benefit from it!
All she ever wanted
was to earn your approval!
Well, I did not ask her to commit plunder!
And more importantly,
I did not ask her to get caught!
Whatever happened to Emilia
was her own fault,
so let her rot in jail!
Well, if you aren't going to help Emilia,
you might as well tell her the truth!
The truth?
What is it?
What truth are you talking about, huh?!
-Answer me!
-Hands off me!
If you don't answer properly,
I'll make sure that Emilia
will rot in jail!
Why are you so furious with Emilia?!
Is it because you think of her
as a weak woman?
Or because of her true identity?!
That her real mother is not Esmeralda?!
That, Julio…
That is your biggest secret!
Yes! I admit it!
Esmeralda is not the mother of Emilia.
Your sister just happened to be my wife
but I never loved her!
Is that what you wanted to hear?!
Huh? Is that it?!
That's not the secret
that I'm referring to!
I'm talking about the woman
who tricked you!
Now, do I dare mention her name?
[Julio] Shut the hell up!
You don't mention her name in my house
nor in my presence!
You, the king of this town!
The almighty Julio that
is worshipped by the people…
-Shut up!
-…was played
and tricked by a woman!
The woman that you hated the most!
-The woman you called weak!
-Yes!
I stole our daughter!
I stole Emilia to punish her!
I want our child to experience the pain
that I suffered from her mother!
And to take my revenge
against that filthy woman!
You're a demon, Julio!
I will tell her the truth!
She can help Emilia to get away
from a demon like you!
Go ahead! [laughing]
Go ahead! Let me see you try!
Let's see, if she'll come down
from her pedestal
to help her daughter!
A daughter that she never met!
A daughter that she never loved!
What do you know about love?!
-You have no right to love!
-You witch!
You have no right to be a father
if you can't get Emilia out
of this miserable fate that has been
brought about by your name!
Pathetic old man!
Clarita! Clarita!
[groaning loudly]
Guard!
[Claire] Driver. Driver.
[guard] Yes, sir?
Go after Clarita!
Don't let her leave this town!
Shoot her if you have to!
But do not let her leave this place alive!
Go! Go!
Clarita! Run for your life!
[groaning loudly]
[tense music playing]
[engine revving]
-[gunshot]
-[grunts]
[gunshot]
-[goon] Let's go.
-[engine revs]
[mumbling] Emilia.
[coughs and groans]
[Emilia] Wait.
I think that's Aunt Claire.
Stop the car!
That's Aunt Claire!
Oh my God!
Aunt Claire! Auntie!
Oh my God! Auntie!
Who did this to you?! Auntie!
Who shot you?!
Auntie, who did this to you?
Esmeralda is not…
your real mother.
[whimpering] Auntie!
Auntie!
Please don't!
[wailing] Auntie!
[pants]
[panting]
[groaning loudly]
[line ringing]
[phone hangs up]
[gasping slowly]
Miss Camia, we're here.
[gasping]
[suspenseful music playing]
What happened here?
[whimpers] Dante?
Mom?
Dante?
Dante!
Mom!
Dad?
[tense music playing]
Your money is already secured.
It's a good thing that Julio
didn't get his hands on it.
The money isn't important, Diego.
What matters is you're safe.
You're all safe.
Are you sure Miss Aguas
is responsible for this screwup?
I'm sure, Congressman.
We'll make her pay for it.
Make sure to find the location of Emilia.
[Damian] Camia?
I'm sorry, brother.
Looks like I won't just be
reclaiming Jaguar's identity.
I'll be taking Camia's love
from you as well.
Surprised?
[theme music playing]